Guide to the S. Rae Logan Papers 1897-1971
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1897-1968; Series VII; 0.5 linear feet
  - Family photographs, undated (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Logan 60th birthday, 80th birthday, 1945, 1965 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - 1951-1952 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - [National Bison Range], undated (Box-folder 14/4)
  - University of North Carolina and Chapel Hill, professors and classmates, [1908] (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Confederate States Veterans & Friends and courthouse, [illegible], North Carolina, 1897 (Box-folder 14/6)
    S. R. Logan second from right, front row. File also contains North Carolina currency from Civil War.
  - District #28, Missoula County, Montana, undated (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Frank Graham, Ben Washburn, Charles Amos Buck, undated (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Hardin, Montana, school, undated (Box-folder 14/9)
  - S. Rae Logan, [1904]-1968 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Logan family, undated (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Winnetka schools, undated (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Family and professional, undated (Box-folder 14/13)